http://www.spellcheck.net/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy for www.spellcheck.net
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally
Identifiable Information'
(PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information
that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to
identify an
individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect,
use, protect or otherwise
handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?
We do not collect personal information from visitors of our site.
When do we collect information?
We collect non-personal information from you when you visit our site. Like many other Web sites, www.spellcheck.net
makes use of log files.
The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet
Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and
number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather
demographic information.
IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Hosted spell-checking service privacy
All text data that is spell-checked by a Hosted service is sent to our server.
Text data is processed and sent back to the client. Spell-checked content and user information is not collected.
Separate words are collected anonymously; we store in logs user activity for further service improvements,
specifically misspelled words,
the action performed (change, change all, ignore, add to user dictionary)
and the correct word selected for a misspelled word.
COOKIES
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files that are sent when you visit a website and stored in the browser of the user. If the corresponding Internet page is retrieved, the browser of the user sends back the content of the cookies and thus enables recognition of the user. Certain cookies are automatically deleted after the end of the browser session (so-called session cookies), others are stored for a predetermined time or permanently in the user's browser and then delete themselves (so-called temporary or permanent cookies)
What data is stored in the cookies?
In cookies, no personal data is stored, but only an online identifier.
How can you prevent the use of cookies or delete cookies?
You can deactivate the storage of cookies via your browser settings and delete already stored cookies at any time in your browser (see the section "Technical notes"). Please note, however, that this online offering without cookies may not work or may only work to a limited extent.
Please note, furthermore, that contradictions against the creation of user profiles partly work through a so-called "opt-out cookie". If you delete all cookies, a contradiction may therefore no longer be taken into account and must be collected again by you.
What cookies do we use?
Analysis cookies
We use analysis cookies in order to be able to record the usage behavior (eg clicked advertising banners, visited sub-pages, made search queries) of our users and to evaluate them in statistical form.
Advertising cookies of third parties
We also allow other companies to collect our users' data through advertising cookies. This allows us and third parties to provide users of our online service with interest-based advertising based on an analysis of their usage behavior (eg, clicked banner ads, visited subpages, requested search queries), and not limited to our online offerings.
Spellcheck.net delivers advertising banners on behalf of its customers. All our banners use cookies. We place these banners on third-party websites, such as a news page, with the help of third-party providers.
Spellcheck.net takes reasonable steps to protect any information we process from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or notification. We take physical, electronic and procedural security measures to protect the data we process. By doing so, we restrict access to this information to authorized employees.
For the cookies that our third-party advertisers place for advertising purposes, we refer to the disclaimers that they have provided on the topic on their own websites. Note that we can only refer to these disclaimers, as they change regularly and Spellcheck.net has no control over them.
How Google will use your personal data
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.spellcheck.net. You can read more details about how Google will use your personal data, via this link.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.spellcheck.net and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
OTHER / UNFORESEEN COOKIES
Due to the way in which the Internet and websites work, it is possible that we do not always have oversight into the cookies that are placed through our banners by third parties. This is particularly the case when our banners contain embedded elements such as texts, documents, images or film clips that are stored by another party, but that are shown on, in or through our banners.
Should you encounter cookies on this website that fall into this category which we have not mentioned above, please let us know or contact the third party directly and ask which cookies they have placed, what the reason for this is, what the lifetime of the cookie is and in what way they have safeguarded your privacy.
Third Party Ad Services and Providers
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.
Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Grammarly, and other affiliate programs and advertising networks.
These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.spaellcheck.net send directly to your browsers. They may automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.spellcheck.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.spellcheck.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
How to Opt-Out
You can opt-out of seeing personalized Google ads by visiting this link - https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en.
You can opt-out of seeing personalized Freestar ads by visiting this link - https://freestar.io/data-policy/
Regarding other third-party advertisers we use on spellcheck.net, you should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.
Security
We have taken every reasonable step to safeguard and to help prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. However, no data transmission over the Internet or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and we cannot anticipate all potential misuse of data over the Internet. Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and your use of the Site indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.
EDAA
We adhere to the EDAA Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. EDAA principally acts as the central licensing body for the OBA Icon and provides technical means for consumers to exercise transparency and control over OBA through the youronlinechoices.eu online consumer choice platform. EDAA is governed by EU-level organizations which make up the value chain of OBA within Europe and acts to ensure European consistency in approach. Click here to learn more about the EDAA.
Changes to Policy
From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy. Therefore, it is recommended that you read it periodically. All substantial changes made to this policy will be notified on the website, at our sole discretion, and will take effect immediately.
Governing Law
This Privacy Policy shall be governed exclusively by the laws of the State of Nevada without regard to any conflict of law provisions. You agree that any legal action to enforce this Privacy Policy shall be brought in the federal or state courts located in Las Vegas, Nevada, and you hereby consent to the exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue of the courts located in Las Vegas, Nevada.
Contact us
Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy via e-mail to: info@domainoptions.net
Our Mailing Address is:
DomainOptions, Inc., 7260 W Azure Dr Ste 140-829, Las Vegas, NV 89130
Word of the day
Etnas
perchused
more
Articles:
